<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yo-kai Watch Technical Knowledge Base on Yo-kai Watch TKB</title>
    <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yo-kai Watch Technical Knowledge Base on Yo-kai Watch TKB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CTRPluginFramework</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/tutorials/ctrpf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 15:45:11 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/tutorials/ctrpf/</guid>
      <description>CTRPluginFramework (CTRPF) is a framework for programmatically modding 3DS games. While it is mainly intended to be used as a template for developers to make mod menus and such, it has some very useful memory hacking features on its own. CTRPF can run on both real hardware and through emulation.
Installation (3DS) Make sure you have the latest Luma3DS
Download the .3gx file from the CTRPF releases.
Rename the file to default.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yo-kai Names - Yo-kai Watch 1</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/yokai-names/ykw1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 11:52:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/yokai-names/ykw1/</guid>
      <description>Internal Name Yo-kai Name y001000 Whisper y001001 Whisper y006000 Pandle y011000 Pandle y011500 Pandull (Criminal) y012000 Undy y014000 Tanbo y016000 D&amp;rsquo;wanna y017000 N&amp;rsquo;more y019000 Q&amp;rsquo;wit y021000 Mochismo y021500 Mochisless (Criminal) y022000 Minochi y031000 Cutta-nah y032000 Cutta-nah-nah y034000 Slacka-slash y041000 Chansin y041500 Chaninverse (Criminal) y042000 Sheen y042500 Shin (Criminal) y043000 Snee y044000 Gleam y051000 Helmsman y052000 Reuknight y052500 Fi-knight (Criminal) y053000 Corptain y061000 Blazion y061500 Blazioff (Criminal) y062000 Quaken y063000 Siro y071000 Beetler y071500 Cheatler (Criminal) y072000 Beetall y073000 Cruncha y081000 Benkei y082000 B3-NK1 y091000 Zerberker y091500 Zeroberker (Criminal) y092000 Snartle y101000 Snotsolong y102000 Duchoo y106000 Espy y106500 Falspy (Criminal) y107000 Infour y111000 Wazzat y111500 Recap (Criminal) y112000 Dummkap y121000 Lafalotta y122000 Blips y126000 Sushiyama y126500 Sushinoma (Criminal) y127000 Kapunki y131000 Cupistol y131500 Impistol (Criminal) y132000 Casanuva y134000 Casanono y141000 Tattletell y141500 Tattletwin (Criminal) y142000 Tattlecast y143000 Skranny y151000 Baku y152000 Whapir y161000 Signibble y162000 Signiton y164000 Statiking y171000 Mirapo y172000 Mircle y181000 Illoo y181500 Illow (Criminal) y182000 Elloo y183000 Alloo y191000 Frostina y191500 Falsina (Criminal) y192000 Blizzaria y193000 Damona y201000 Kyubi y202000 Frostail y211000 Dulluma y212000 Darumacho y214000 Goruma y221000 Coughkoff y222000 Hurchin y231000 Dazzabel y231500 Dullabel (Criminal) y232000 Rattelle y234000 Skelebella y241000 Noway y242000 Impass y244000 Walldin y251000 Blowkade y252000 Ledballoon y261000 Armsman y271000 Mad Mountain y272000 Lava Lord y281000 Rhinoggin y281500 Rhinopposite (Criminal) y282000 Rhinormous y283000 Hornaplenty y293000 Castelius III y294000 Castelius II y295000 Castelius I y295500 Castelilose (Criminal) y296000 Castelius Max y301000 Dromp y302000 Swosh y311000 Cadin y311500 Cadout (Criminal) y312000 Cadable y314000 Singcada y321000 Buhu y321500 Buher (Criminal) y322000 Flumpy y323000 Skreek y331000 Jibanyan y331500 Doppelnyan y332000 Thornyan y333000 Baddinyan y334000 Robonyan y335000 Goldenyan y336000 Dianyan y337000 Sapphinyan y338000 Emenyan y339000 Rubinyan y340000 Topanyan y341000 Walkappa y341500 Watkappa (Criminal) y342000 Appak y342500 Pakka (Criminal) y343000 Supyo y351000 Komasan y351500 Komasham (Criminal) y352000 Komane y352500 Koshame (Criminal) y353000 Komajiro y354000 Komiger y361000 Daiz y361500 Daizn&amp;rsquo;t (Criminal) y362000 Confuze y371000 Pupsicle y372000 Chilhuahua y372500 Fussky (Criminal) y373000 Swelterrier y381000 Fidgephant y382000 Touphant y391000 Rollen y392000 Dubbles y401000 Tengu y401500 Zerogu (Criminal) y402000 Flengu y411000 Hungramps y411500 Fullgramps (Criminal) y412000 Hungorge y413000 Grainpa y421000 Manjimutt y421500 Manjimitate (Criminal) y422000 Multimutt y424000 Sir Berus y431000 Heheheel y431500 Conger (Criminal) y432000 Croonger y433000 Urnaconda y441000 Enerfly y441500 Enofly (Criminal) y442000 Enefly y443000 Betterfly y444000 Peppillon y451000 Wiglin y451500 Trippa (Criminal) y452000 Steppa y453000 Rhyth y461000 Shmoopie y461500 Whoopie (Criminal) y462000 Pinkipoo y463000 Pookivil y471000 Happierre y472000 Reversa y473000 Reversette y481000 Ol&amp;rsquo; Saint Trick y481500 Ol&amp;rsquo; Slap Stick (Criminal) y482000 Ol&amp;rsquo; Fortune y491000 Mama Aura y492000 Auntie Heart y501000 Papa Bolt y501500 Papa Dolt (Criminal) y502000 Uncle Infinite y511000 Ake y512000 Payn y514000 Agon y521000 Negatibuzz y521500 Negatibuzz-kill (Criminal) y522000 Moskevil y524000 Scritchy y531000 Leadoni y532000 Mynimo y541000 Peckpocket y542000 Rockabelly y551000 Chatalie y552000 Nagatha y560000 Bruff y561000 Roughraff y561500 Roughraffony (Criminal) y562000 Badude y571000 Negasus y571500 Bogusus (Criminal) y572000 Neighfarious y581000 Grumples y581500 Grimples (Criminal) y582000 Everfore y582500 Neverfore (Criminal) y583000 Eterna y591000 Cheeksqueek y592000 Cuttincheez y601000 Compunzer y601500 Blamedian (Criminal) y602000 Lamedian y611000 Insomni y611500 Apni (Criminal) y612000 Sandi y621000 Dimmy y622000 Blandon y623000 Nul y631000 Droplette y632000 Drizzle y633000 Slush y634000 Alhail y635000 Gush y641000 Dismarelda y642000 Dismarelda y651000 Wantston y652000 Grubsnitch y661000 Hidabat y662000 Abodabat y663000 Belfree y670000 Chippa y671000 Lodo y671500 Lodon&amp;rsquo;t (Criminal) y680000 Nird y681000 Tengloom y681500 Fouwl (Criminal) y691000 Suspicioni y692000 Tantroni y693000 Contrarioni y701000 Timidevil y701500 Mimicevil (Criminal) y702000 Beelzebold y703000 Count Cavity y711000 Greesel y711500 Geezel (Criminal) y712000 Awevil y721000 Noko y721500 Nogo (Criminal) y722000 Bloominoko y723000 Pandanoko y731000 Draggie y731500 Shaggie (Criminal) y732000 Dragon Lord y733000 Azure Dragon y741000 Fishpicable y742000 Rageon y744000 Tunatic y751000 Chummer y751500 Bummer (Criminal) y752000 Shrook y760000 Almi y761000 Spenp y761500 Sdend (Criminal) y771000 Babblong y772000 Bananose y781000 Copperled y781500 Copyled (Criminal) y782000 Slitheref y783000 Slitheref y791000 Venoct y791001 Venoct (Cutscene) y792000 Shad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Names - Yo-kai Watch 3</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/map-names/ykw3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 10:28:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/map-names/ykw3/</guid>
      <description>Internal Name Location t001b01 Geragera Train Cabin 1 Battle Bg t001b02 Headasteam Boss Background t001b03 Geragera Train Cabin 2 Battle Bg t001b11 Paradise Springs Battle Bg t001b12 Gera Gera Land Battle Bg t001b13 Wolfit Down Battle Bg t001b15 Kabuking Boss Background t001b21 Yopple Battle Bg t001b23 Yopple-Bot Boss Background t001b31 Old Yo-kai World 1 Battle Bg t001b32 Old Yo-kai World 2 Battle Bg t001b33 Old Yo-kai World 3 Battle Bg t001b35 Old Yo-kai World 4 Battle Bg t001b37 Old Yo-kai World Liar Mountain Battle Bg t001b39 Old Yo-kai World Hooligan Road Battle Bg t001b41 Old Yo-kai World Hungry Pass Battle Bg t001b43 McKraken Boss Background t001b51 New Yo-kai City Battle Bg t001b53 New Yo-kai City Park Battle Bg t001b55 Bada-Bing Tower Battle Bg t001b57 Bada-Bing Tower Moon Battle Bg t001b59 Ghoulfather Boss Background t001b61 Don Spiracy Boss Background t001b71 Rongo Swirll Boss Background t001d01 Paradise Springs Entrance t001d02 Gera Gera Land Entrance t001d03 Wolfit Down Entrance t001d05 Paradise Springs t001d06 Gera Gera Land t001d07 Wolfit Down t001d08 Kaibuki Theater t001d09 Kaibuki Theater Basement t001d21 Yopple HQ Garden t001d23 Yopple HQ Lobby t001d25 Yopple HQ CEO&amp;rsquo;s Office t001d27 Yopple HQ Yo-kai Watch Center t001d29 Yopple HQ Meeting Room t001d31 Yopple HQ Lab t001d33 Yopple HQ Assembly Line t001d35 Yopple HQ Fighting Room t001d37 Yopple HQ Cafeteria t001d39 Yopple HQ The Fish Tank t001d41 Ambrosia Pavilion Entrance (Yo-kai world Entrance) t001d42 Yo-kai world t001d46 Ambrosia Pavilion t001d49 Treasure Ship of the Seven Gods t001d51 Bada-Bing Tower Lobby t001d53 Bada-Bing Tower Elevator t001d55 Dangerous Floor t001g00 New Yo-kai City t101g00 Uptown Springdale t101i01 Nate&amp;rsquo;s house F1 t101i02 Nate&amp;rsquo;s house F2 t101i03 Katie&amp;rsquo;s House F1 t101i04 Katie&amp;rsquo;s House F2 t101i10 Logan&amp;rsquo;s House t101i21 Banter Bakery t101i23 Everymart Uptown t101i25 Springdale Community Center t101i27 Piggleston Bank t101i29 Lambert Post Office t101i31 Jungle Hunter t101i35 Memory Store t101i51 Springdale Elementary 1F South t101i52 Springdale Elementary 1F North t101i53 Springdale Elementary 2F t101i55 Springdale Elementary 3F t101i58 Springdale Elementary Roof t101i59 Springdale Elementary Gym t102d01 Mt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Names - Yo-kai Watch 2</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/map-names/ykw2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 10:15:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/map-names/ykw2/</guid>
      <description>Internal Name Location t001d01 Paradise Springs Entrance t001d02 Gera Gera Land Entrance t001d03 Wolfit Down Entrance t001d05 Paradise Springs t001d06 Gera Gera Land t001d07 Wolfit Down t001d08 Kaibuki Theater t001d09 Kaibuki Theater Basement t001d41 Yo-kai world Entrance t001d42 Yo-kai world t001d43 Liar Mountain t001d44 Hooligan Road t001d45 Hungry Pass t001s00 Unknown (Hexpress?) t001s01 Paradise Springs Station t001s02 Gera Gera Land Station t001s03 Wolfit Down Station t100d00 Underground Waterway t101d01 Shady Back Alley t101d02 Lonely Waterway t101d02c Lonely Waterway (Copy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Names - Yo-kai Watch 1</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/map-names/ykw1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 17:30:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/game-data/map-names/ykw1/</guid>
      <description>Internal Name Location t100b01 Uptown Springdale Grass Battle BG t100b02 Mt. Wildwood Grass Battle BG t100b03 Catfish Pond Battle BG t100b04 Uptown Springdale Water Battle BG t100b05 Breezy Hills Gourd Pond Battle BG t100b06 SV Snaggerjag Boss BG t100b21 Alley Battle BG t100b22 Downtown Springdale Alley Battle BG t100b23 Shopper&amp;rsquo;s Row Alley Battle BG t100b24 Blossom Heights Battle BG t100b27 Tranquility Apt. Battle BG t100b51 Regular Generic Battle BG t100b52 Special Generic Battle BG t100b53 PvP Battle BG t100d00 Underground Waterway t101b01 Uptown Springdale Battle BG t101b02 Nate&amp;rsquo;s house Battle BG t101b03 Katie&amp;rsquo;s house Battle BG t101b21 School Battle BG t101b23 Springdale Elementary Bathroom Battle BG t101b25 Springdale Elementary Outside Battle BG t101d01 Shady Back Alley t101d02 Lonely Waterway t101d03 The Catwalk t101d05 Desolate Lane t101g00 Uptown Springdale t101i01 Nate&amp;rsquo;s house F1 t101i02 Nate&amp;rsquo;s house F2 t101i03 Katie&amp;rsquo;s House F1 t101i04 Katie&amp;rsquo;s House F2 t101i21 Banter Bakery t101i23 Everymart Uptown t101i25 Springdale Community Center t101i27 Piggleston Bank t101i29 Lambert Post Office t101i31 Jungle Hunter t101i51 Springdale Elementary 1F South t101i52 Springdale Elementary 1F North t101i53 Springdale Elementary 2F t101i55 Springdale Elementary 3F t101i58 Springdale Elementary Roof t101i59 Springdale Elementary Gym t102b01 Mt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.xc</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/xc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:19:17 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/xc/</guid>
      <description>Magic Number (ASCII) Magic Number (HEX) File Type XPCK 0x5850434b Archive This is a general archive format used to compress a lot of the game&amp;rsquo;s files. All 3d models, textures, armature, and some sprites are stored in these archives. They are identical to .xa and .xk files other than their extention name.
Kuriimu2 is able to extract, modify, and repack these archives.
Tinifan&amp;rsquo;s Level-5 Blender Addon can export external 3d models into a format that Yo-kai Watch can use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.xi</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/xi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 15:59:08 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/xi/</guid>
      <description>Magic Number (ASCII) Magic Number (HEX) File Type IMGC00 0x494D47433030 Image This is the image container used by all Yo-kai Watch games. It supports many different image formats, but ETC1 and ETC1A4 seem to be used the most.
Kuriimu2 can extract, convert, and replace these files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.cfg.bin</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/cfg-bin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 16:32:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/cfg-bin/</guid>
      <description>Magic Number (ASCII) Magic Number (HEX) File Type N/A N/A Data A binary file format for storing data. It is used for NPC/menu dialogue, items at stores, objects on the map, etc. It is the binary form of .cfg files, although leftover files show that they have a few different extensions, including .ptree and .mapenv.
For just editing dialogue, Kuriimu works well. If you need to edit other types of the format, Tinifan&amp;rsquo;s CfgBinEditor or a hex editor will work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.fa</title>
      <link>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 16:15:31 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yokai.chaoticpumpk.in/file-formats/fa/</guid>
      <description>Magic Number (ASCII) Magic Number (HEX) File Type ARC0 0x41524330 Archive This is the archive used in all of the Yo-kai Watch games, located in the root of the RomFS.
Kuriimu2 is able to extract, modify, and repack these archives.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
